beeradvocate.com 2017-11-19

# General - Privacy Policy | Community | BeerAdvocate

Dismiss Notice

**Extreme Beer Fest: Los Angeles**

Join us December 9th in Los Angeles for the ultimate throwdown of craft beer creativity! 

  1. 

### 

BeerAdvocate _Founders (17,635)_ _Aug 23, 1996_ _Massachusetts_

_**Subscriber**_

> **BeerAdvocate.com Privacy Policy**
> 
> This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for this web site ("Service"), and applies solely to information collected by this Service.
> 
> **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
>  The providers ("we", "us", "our") are the sole owners of the information collected by our Service. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
> 
> We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
> 
> Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
> 
> **Registration**  
>  In order to use this Service, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name, email address and location). This information is used to tailor your experience and contact you about items on our Service in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.
> 
> **Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
>  You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by editing your profile information or contacting us via email:
> 
>     * See what data we have about you, if any.
>     * Change/correct any data we have about you.
>     * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
> **Orders**  
>  We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
> 
> **Cookies**  
>  We use "cookies" on this Service. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a Service visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our Service and identify repeat visitors to our Service. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Service. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Service. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our Service.
> 
> Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Service (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
> 
> **Links**  
>  This Service contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Service and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
> 
> **Surveys & Contests**  
>  From time-to-time our Service requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this Service.
> 
> **Security**  
>  We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Service, your information is protected both online and offline.
> 
> Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
> 
> While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
> 
> **Updates**  
>  Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time without notice, however, all updates will be posted on this page.
> 
> If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should [contact us immediately](http://www.beeradvocate.com/contact/).
